I swore you were Tony yeah I swore it was true you laughed it off said psyche I'm
just me not that dude you're ready to crash out when the moment feels right
top-donator energy you light up the night big brother in the chat
I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
You're funny as hell, yeah, it's always a blast
These moments we're making are built to last
Thank you, ghost, you're one of a kind
With your big heart and mischief and your quick fire mind
Got that ring
In your quick-fire mind
I won't forget you
Not Tony, huh?
Alright, ghost, I believe you.
Maybe.
Steel screen, black mirror eyes
You talk divine while the signal dies
Born in static, forged in flame
Every troll got a goddamn name
Psyche in the towel, storm in his head
Terrorites on fire, the spirits are fed
Father of madness, the cat Daddy King
The Lord's at his feet to let the panther sing
Every click is a confession
in the chat.
I'm calling it from the beach with this beautiful beach today
I just woke up
So I like one of the weirdest dreams, here's what I remember
I was getting like some kind of like
Biller or like plastic surgery
And I was like in
Hollywood or like Los Angeles or something and I go into
The clinic and guess who is there
All three extra
It's the queen of nightmares herself. Let me see
This is a good one. Yeah, this is this lady
She was there this lady was there getting some filler, too. I
Don't know she needs any. I don't know. I she doesn't want me to talk about her. But I have to
Yeah, she was there
Kidding some kind of treatment
But it was basically a nightmare of a place. So I was with this guy. He was really cute
I think I met I think it's okay. I met on tiktok, but um
And he kept like interfering with like the surgery.
He was getting something done too, right?
And so, but then he'd like,
they kept trying to give me shots and like different,
like, you know, anesthesia and stuff like that.
And he kept like,
like taking them and trying to get high on them.
Like he would grab it and he'd like sniff it.
And I would like, I'm like, stop.
And so I was like, okay, he has to be in a different room.
Especially like he wasn't a different room.
But and I was just mad because he got trying to interfere and then things just kept going wrong
With like the people that work there, I mean everyone was crazy they were like
Kept like preparing me for surgery and like I was awake and I was like I was just weirdest dream ever, okay
Hey, Jamie. Hey, Ilya. Halo the god. Hey everyone's here money for 20 bring a joint
Hello, how's everybody?
So I don't know if I got any filler, but yeah, that lady was there
Emma Leviathan was there
I don't know if she was like and I was like it's psyche. It's I remember I say it's psyche and she was like, huh, huh, I
Don't think she really cared
I don't think she talked to me or anything, but it was kind of funny.
Okay, that's a woke up today. I had a message from ghost.
This guy, he wants ghost Tilbur.
Um, he's excited.
Okay, you know what's that fun? I tried to tell him
as a ghost, I'm having problems right now
Don't call page a dumb dumb. They don't you better like be polite, please
It was so rude to page page hadn't been here for like oh probably a month. Yeah
But though it's gonna be scary and then he was just and then she was trying to get like give him a nice reading and stuff
And she and then of course he just pissed her off and then you know she left and it's like
Yeah, a little bit rude goes and so it goes how about
And I know go and ghost did donate a lot and it's a yes. I think he donated like
Maybe over a hundred dollars last night, and so I'm gonna I want him to have a lot of fun. Okay
But at the same time, let's
Keep it like a little bit friendlier. I don't know if it makes sense. Okay
Okay, ghost
Yes, you can have your ghost over, okay, how do we get this off the screen?
Yeah, I'm luckily I'm calling from a beautiful beach and so
I mean, I woke up, it's great to do this, okay?
There's stuff I need to do, but I'm doing this.
Okay?
Because we have a request, very special friend of the show.
Yep.
Okay.
Have eaten I have I have like I think I smoke my last cigarette that I have I
Check my DMs, okay. I
Know I just
Wow, how are you good? There's a leg
I do feel a little better. I feel a little better.
So, uh, oh, thank you so much.
Thank you, Jamie. Okay, who wants to come up?
Ghost, are you here?
Well, we can play the, they can play the perry page song or waiting.
Oh, it happens. Hold on.
That's Prairie Page
Cards on the table
Incense in the air
Tarot spread open
She reads like a prayer
Every word she speaks feels like a golden page
Oh prairie page, wild and free, cool
There's a breeze through the evergreens
Alexander's heart's gone all the way lost
And that smile in those prairie days, yeah, she's a sweetheart
A real I made
That's my Canadian bed
my prairie page
The spark in the flame
Okay, well, thanks a lot, Alexander,
because when I get donations, okay,
that does make a difference when the video is demonetized,
okay, it does make a difference, okay?
So, Alexander, you're gonna owe me if, okay, oh, God,
they're giving me a chance to edit, hold on.
You have to tell me, is it more than that,
you said, is it more than the one thing, okay?
What time was it, was it, okay, you have to tell me,
I can't edit it.
And why would you do that? Okay?
There's one thing. Okay. I think I think I know where it is
Was it like a 20 20 the 22 minutes 125 30? Okay. Oh
Hold on
What don't do that shit Alex? Why do you fucking mess with my stuff? That's messing with my money, okay? Don't do that shit like
It's not easy to do I don't know how to do it yeah, oh god damn it. I'll be right back